<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conclusion on AWS DevSecOps Modernization Workshop</title>
    <link>http://localhost/50_conclusion.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conclusion on AWS DevSecOps Modernization Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/50_conclusion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulations</title>
      <link>http://localhost/50_conclusion/1_after_thoughts.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost/50_conclusion/1_after_thoughts.html</guid>
      <description>Well Done Congratulations. You have completed this DevSecOps workshop on shifting security testing left.
Recap on what you have learned  Learned how to deploy CloudFormation stacks Learned about a modern CI/CD pipeline Learned how to test in AWS CodeBuild Learned about a couple of open source tools for security testing Learned why it is important to test as early as possible in the pipeline  Final Thoughts Due to the time and scope of the workshop there are several things that can and should be instrumented to improve security testing within the CI/CD pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleanup</title>
      <link>http://localhost/50_conclusion/10_cleanup.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost/50_conclusion/10_cleanup.html</guid>
      <description>Cleanup In order to prevent charges to your account we recommend cleaning up the infrastructure that was created. If you plan to keep things running so you can examine the workshop a bit more please remember to do the cleanup when you are done. It is very easy to leave things running in an AWS account, forget about it, and then accrue charges.
You will need to manually delete some resources before you delete the CloudFormation stacks so please do the following steps in order.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>